=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 6=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 6 =
Get out.
اخرج.
If Qingmu didn't insist on marrying you,
إذا لم يصر تشينغمو على الزواج منك ،
you can never enter Li family's residence.
لا يمكنك أبدًا دخول مسكن عائلة Li.
It's good that you're here.
من الجيد أنك هنا.
There's a score I need to even with you.
هناك نتيجة أحتاجها حتى معك.
What?
ماذا؟
Why are you pretending?
لماذا تتظاهر؟
Get down from my bed now.
انزل من سريري الآن.
Your bed?
سريرك؟
Lanhua is my chosen daughter-in-law.
Lanhua هي زوجة ابني المختارة.
Granduncle gave us some money
أعطانا Granduncle بعض المال
but Qingmu used it to buy medicine for you.
لكن Qingmu استخدمه لشراء الدواء لك.
Aren't you a jinx?
ألست النحس؟
Get out of Li family.
اخرج من عائلة لي.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I'm
انا
kind.
طيب القلب.
I'll just keep you here as a maid.
سأبقيك هنا كخادمة.
I'm a little thirsty.
أنا عطشان قليلاً.
What are you waiting for? Pour some tea for her!
ماذا تنتظر؟  صب بعض الشاي لها!
Useless!
عديم الفائدة!
Don't you even know how to brew tea?
ألا تعرف حتى كيف تصنع الشاي؟
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
The medicine store is still losing and owing others money.
لا يزال متجر الأدوية يخسر ويدين للآخرين بأموال.
My father
والدي
has prepared the money to
أعدت المال ل
pay his son-in-law's debt.
دفع ديون صهره.
What a shame that
يا له من عار
Qingmu can't become his son-in-law.
لا يمكن أن يصبح Qingmu صهره.
Otherwise, he doesn't have to worry about the examination fee.
خلاف ذلك ، لا داعي للقلق بشأن رسوم الامتحان.
Then,
ثم،
Qingmu would rather have debt than marry you.
تفضل Qingmu الديون على الزواج منك.
Why is that?
لماذا هذا؟
Pang Longyue!
بانغ لونجيو!
I wanted to keep you here as a maid!
أردت أن أبقيك هنا كخادمة!
Don't force me to chase you out and sleep in the street.
لا تجبرني على مطاردتك والنوم في الشارع.
Okay, don't be angry.
حسنًا ، لا تغضب.
Let me pour you some tea.
دعني أسكب لك بعض الشاي.
That's more like it.
وهذا أشبه ذلك.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
آسف ، لم أقصد ذلك.
I didn't hold it tight.
لم أحكم عليه بشدة.
You did it on purpose!
فعلت ذلك عن قصد!
Let me pour you another cup.
اسمح لي أن أسكب لك فنجانًا آخر.
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
You...
أنت...
Me what?
ماذا عني؟
Mother!
الأم!
Mother, she was hiding in the closet, eating and having fun.
أمي ، كانت مختبئة في الخزانة ، تأكل وتستمتع.
I found out
اكتشفت
and she's bullying me.
وهي تتنمر علي.
Who?
من؟
Me.
أنا.
I've chased you out.
لقد طاردتك.
How dare you come back?
كيف تجرؤ على العودة؟
In this house,
في هذا المنزل،
no one else has the right to chase me out besides Qingmu.
لا أحد لديه الحق في مطاردتي إلى جانب Qingmu.
You bad girl.
أنت فتاة سيئة.
Okay.
تمام.
Let me show you if I have the right or not.
دعني أوضح لك ما إذا كان لدي الحق أم لا.
You unfilial son.
أنت ابن غير مخلص.
If you keep protecting her,
إذا واصلت حمايتها ،
I'll disown you.
سوف تبرأ منك.
I'll listen to you.
سوف استمع اليك.
I'll divorce Longyue and marry Lanhua.
سأطلق Longyue وأتزوج Lanhua.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Dear.
عزيزي.
Yes.
نعم.
Lanhua is still better.
Lanhua لا تزال أفضل.
You've finally come to your senses.
لقد وصلت أخيرًا إلى حواسك.
Chen family is so generous.
عائلة تشن كريمة جدا.
We must treat Lanhua well.
يجب أن نتعامل مع Lanhua جيدًا.
You all know that
كلكم تعرفون ذلك
Lanhua wants to get some maids, don't you?
لانهوا تريد الحصول على بعض الخادمات ، أليس كذلك؟
My requirements are not high.
متطلباتي ليست عالية.
I just need two maids.
أنا فقط بحاجة إلى خادمتين.
We can't afford to hire a maid.
لا يمكننا تحمل تكلفة استئجار خادمة.
From now on,
من الان فصاعدا،
sister-in-law and mother will become the maids.
ستصبح أخت الزوج والأم خادمات.
Mother is not young anymore.
الأم ليست صغيرة بعد الآن.
How can she do the chores?
كيف يمكنها القيام بالأعمال المنزلية؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
She's just assisting you.
انها مجرد مساعدتك.
You have to do most of the chores.
عليك القيام بمعظم الأعمال المنزلية.
No.
رقم.
Mother,
الأم،
we're not able to serve a rich lady.
لسنا قادرين على خدمة سيدة ثرية.
Mother, who do you think
أمي ، من تعتقد
is better between Lanhua and Longyue?
أفضل بين Lanhua و Longyue؟
Longyue is better.
Longyue أفضل.
Mother!
الأم!
If that won't work,
إذا لم ينجح ذلك ،
I just want Pang Longyue as my maid.
أريد فقط أن تكون بانج لونجي خادمة.
No way.
مستحيل.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Because Longyue is my wife.
لأن Longyue هي زوجتي.
You're too much!
انت مبالغ فيه!
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪